around the world with lights out sports
update go Bob battery here welcome to
the lights out sports update bringing
you stunning examples of athleticism
from around the globe we begin tonight
in Tokyo a city still healing after
getting its kicked in by goddamn
Godzilla the competitive eating world
was rocked by this week's hundred and
twenty third annual noodle sucking
Jamboree look at these winners just
power blasting through a metric ton of
ramen they're really packing it in I
mean if you're a starving kid watching
this it's got to be tough I haven't seen
someone slurp this many noodles in one
sitting
since my four ex-wife on her honeymoon
we go now to California in the pro-am
hacky sack circuit a place with more
dorks per square inch than the Geek
Squad
now this kids putting on a display so
graceful so inspiring the guy in the
black t-shirt can't help but stare at
his phone through the whole thing he
doesn't give a hot squirt of piss about
this his girlfriend's kid
dragged him to and look at that victory
this kid is truly the greatest winner in
a sport for losers I hope this kid's got
rubbers because he's about to be neck
deep in the pod lagoon now to teach
wisdom Transylvania's something who
gives it let's look at some morons with
swords on guard it's time for the
Renaissance Jamboree here's a bunch of
ding dongs working on overtime to
protect their virginity these guys first
time using wood on something besides an
anime body pillow don't be fooled by the
weapons and skills on display Spade I'm
confident these dudes or a bunch of
who would run for the hills of
real ever hit the fan next up India
Olympic gold medalists and giving people
diarrhea for 4,000 good second of years
and we have a game of what the rest of
the world calls football and we here in
America call change the channel
apparently they went to the literal bull
pen jesus H buttholes what happened this
bull being surprisingly calm while these
little Lords play keep-away with a
monster the size of a goddamn Camaro
the referee is passing by on a
motorcycle
since the game is apparently being
played on fury road this looks like a
remake of Air Bud from a country that
hasn't invented electricity yet and
finally the beaches of Hawaii let's
watch a swarm of morons say aloha to the
wonderful world of drowning
it's the World Surfing Championships
held this year on scenic dunk island
here goes chan getting cut off by Chad
Oh a dab of chat and these Chad's are
dropping like goddamn flies just a true
spectacle of mediocrity that's gonna
wrap it up for tonight's lights-out
sports update back to you in the studio
[Applause]
[Music]
you